

CAREER SUMMARY

My professional background is primarily in video production, live television, and entertainment. I've worked for record labels, production companies, and a media conglomerate (AOL). I approach problems from a technical perspective, to break the larger problems into smaller ones. Working as a team player, I strive to execute the most efficient and effective solutions available.

I proactively sought code-centered side hustles (hobbies) over the years, including nashvillePA.com (2007-2015) to staff production assistants in Nashville, TN, and holyvintage.com (2010-2013), a site that managed an inventory of vintage t-shirts through hard-coded HTML. <--yikes!

In 2019 I became a full-time Software Developer. A comprehensive look at previous employment can be found on my resume, available on my website, below.

TECHNOLOGIES USED

HTML 5 CSS 3 JavaScript React.js Python Django

HOW TO CONTACT ME

Email: landonlanemorgan@gmail.com

Phone: 615-307-0005

Website: iandonmorgan.github.io

LANDON MORGAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Software Developer

Nashville Software School | Nov 2019 - Present

Three-week, JavaScript focused web development jumpstart in November of 2019.

Beginning January of 2020, a six-month, fully immersive full-stack bootcamp with emphasis on:

- · Python/Django for back-end development
- · HTML/CSS utilized to create web pages and applications
- · JavaScript utilized in creating, updating, deleting objects, running object or array methods and functions
- \cdot JSON-server, JSON and API fetch utilized for data management and storage in applications
- · React and react-router-dom utilized for quick and stylish functionality and design

EDUCATION

Nashville Software School

Web and Software Development (Python/Django) Nov 2019 - June 2020

Cohort 38 at Nashville Software School, a full-stack bootcamp with curriculum about Python/Django, and front-end languages including JavaScript, React, CSS3, and HTML5.

University of Oklahoma

Bachelor of Business Administration, Marketing Aug 1999 - Aug 2003

GPA: 3.28 (based on 4pt scale)

Activities and Societies: Campus Activities Council Public Relations Chair, CAC Film Series Chair, Vice-President Kappa Alpha Order, Honors Dorm Resident Advisor, 2003 Homecoming Court

WORK REFERENCES

Scott McDaniel, VP Creative Services

Nashville Convention & Visitors Corp Email: scottm@visitmusiccity.com | Phone: 615-259-4781

Frantz Cayo, Senior Director Programming and Talent

Black Entertainment Television (BET) Email: frantz.cayo@bet.com | Phone: 646-463-4194

Kevin Merritt, Talent Executive

One Foot Productions

Email: kevin@onefootprod.com | Phone: 212-203-1338